badtameezdilmovies.com 2019-06-08

# Privacy Policy - Badtameez Dil Movies

We value the trust placed in use by you and therefore, we follow the highest standards of privacy guidelines to protect the information shared by you with us.

This Privacy Policy (“ **Privacy Policy** ”) governs the use of personal information shared with or collected by BadtameezDilMovies from the users of BadtameezDilMovies. This Privacy Policy is subject to change from time to time without any written notice to you. Please review the Privacy Policy from time to time to be updated with the latest changes and modifications.

By browsing, using, downloading or installing BadtameezDilMovies, you agree to be bound by the terms of this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree with the terms contained herein, please do not download or browse BadtameezDilMovies.

By mere browsing or use of BadtameezDilMovies, you consent to the terms of this Privacy Policy and agree to the use of your personal information in the manner as provided under this Privacy Policy.

All capitalized terms that have not been specifically defined herein shall have the same meaning as provided under the Terms of Use.

This Privacy Policy should be read in conjunction and together with the Terms of Use available on[ http://BadtameezDilMovies.com/terms-of-service/](https://badtameezdilmovies.com/terms-of-service/).

**Collection and Use of Personal Information**  
‘Personal Information’, ‘Information’ and ‘Sensitive Information’ shall have the meaning ascribed to it under the IT Act, 2000 and Information Technology (Reasonable Security Practises and Procedures and Sensitive Personal Data or Information) Rules, 2011.

**Generic Information**

We collect Your Personal Information/Information when you use BadtameezDilMovies and when You share such information with Us through email or by posting on BadtameezDilMovies or by any other means made available to You by Us. During browsing/using of BadtameezDilMovies by You, We collect information with respect to Your IP Address and zip code. In the event You want to share any feedback or raise a concern, We collect information with respect to Your name, age, mobile number, email address, gender, occupation etc.

We collect information in order to provide you with a safe, efficient, smooth and customized experience. This allows us to provide services and features that most likely meet your needs, and to customize BadtameezDilMovies to make your experience safer and easier.

We do not solicit any Sensitive Information about You or seek information with respect to Your credit/debit card, Movies banking or other financial information, except as expressly provided herein. However, if You share such information with Us voluntarily, We will not be liable for any actions, claims, costs, expenses or other liabilities that may arise as a consequence of such any unauthorized use or misuse of such information.

**Demographic Information**

We may track certain information about you based upon your behaviour on BadtameezDilMovies. We use this information for conducting internal research on our users’ demographics, interests, and behaviour to better understand, protect and serve our users. This information is compiled and analysed on an aggregated basis. This information may include the website that you just visited (whether this website is on BadtameezDilMovies or not), which website you next visit, your computer browser information.

We may also collect information to track user behaviour and preferences for internal analytics and research. We may also use Your information: (i) to evaluate Your interest for various genres of content, services, offers; (ii) to perform analytics and conduct customer research, to determine Your interest, for identifying Content that generate sales and to analyse traffic patterns.

If you choose to post messages on our message boards, chat rooms or other message areas or leave feedback, We will collect that information You provide to us. We retain this information as necessary to resolve disputes, provide customer support and troubleshoot problems as permitted by law.

If You send us personal correspondence, such as emails or letters, or if other users or third parties send us correspondence about Your activities or postings on BadtameezDilMovies, we may store such information.

We identify and use Your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer BadtameezDilMovies. Your IP address is also used to help identify You and to gather broad demographic information.

We will occasionally ask You to complete optional online surveys. These surveys may ask You for contact information and demographic information (like zip code, age, or  
income level). We use this data to tailor Your experience at BadtameezDilMovies, providing You with content that We think You might be interested in and to display content according to Your preferences.

**Cookie**

A “cookie” is a small piece of information stored by a web server on a web browser so it can be later read back from that browser. Cookies are useful for enabling the browser to remember information specific to a given user. We place both permanent and temporary cookies in your computer’s hard drive. The cookies do not contain any of your personally identifiable information.

You will always have an option not to provide certain information and can choose to opt-out from provision of certain information.

**Disclosure of Personal Information with Third Parties**  
We may disclose Personal Information to affiliates and group companies. We may also disclose Your Personal Information with third parties strictly on confidential terms. We may disclose such information to third parties in order to provide You access to BadtameezDilMovies and facilitate or Your participation in any contest, game or activity conducted by BadtameezDilMovies, to comply with Our legal obligations, to enforce Terms of Use, to facilitate our marketing and advertising activities, or to prevent, detect, mitigate, and investigate fraudulent or illegal activities related to BadtameezDilMovies.

We will always take Your express consent at the time of sharing your Personal Information with third parties for their marketing and advertising purposes.

In the event of any requirement by court order, government or quasi-government agency to disclose Your Personal Information, We will disclose information as may be legally required. We may also disclose Your Personal Information if we, in the good faith believe that such disclosure is reasonably necessary to respond to subpoenas, court orders, or other legal process.

In the event BadtameezDilMovies is merged with or acquired by another company or in case of re-organization or re-structuring of business, We and our affiliates will share Your Personal Information, wholly or in part, with another business entity.

**Third Party Sites**  
BadtameezDilMovies may provide links to various third party websites that may collect your Personal Information. Use of Your information collected by such third party website will be governed by the privacy policy in such third party website. BadtameezDilMovies has no control on the operation of such third party websites and You may share information with such third party at Your sole risk. BadtameezDilMovies shall not be liable to You for any misappropriation of Your Personal Information by such third party.

**Promotional and Marketing Activities**  
We will send communications to You at regular intervals to notify you of, among other things, various offers, new content, exclusive deals etc., that may be available or new services that may be of interest to You. By accessing BadtameezDilMovies, you expressly consent to receiving such communications from us at regular intervals.

However, if you do not wish to receive any communication from us, You may request to opt-out by writing to us at copyright@BadtameezDilMovies.com. Once, We are in receipt of Your request, We will cease sending promotional messages to You.

**Security and Compliance with Laws**  
We strive to protect Your Personal Information against unauthorized disclosure, misuse, unlawful use, modification, loss or destruction. We take all reasonable measures and precautions, as per standard industry practises, to keep Your Personal Information confidential. We ensure compliance with all applicable laws including but not limited to Information Technology (Reasonable security practices and procedures and sensitive personal data or information) Rules, 2011.

**Contact Us**  
If You require any information or clarification regarding the use of your Personal Information or this Privacy Policy or if You have any grievance with respect to use of Your Personal Information, you can contact us at info@BadtameezDilMovies.com.

**International Use**  
BadtameezDilMovies is a company based in Pakistan. By browsing/using BadtameezDilMovies, YOU hereby acknowledge that BadtameezDilMovies is not responsible or liable in any manner to comply with any local laws of YOUR territory except Pakistan with respect to BadtameezDilMovies
